

ABOUT ME

I've loved art since I was young, mastering crayon drawing at 5 and diving into watercolor painting at 10. I'm most confident with watercolors, where I express my ideas

I'm determined to keep learning new skills, and get better at what I do. In the future, I want to gather lots of experience and achievements to become a skilled professional in both art and gaming design.

My goal is to create cool things for this exciting industry and keep getting better at what I love doing.

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH

MALAY

CHINESE



HOBBIES







PHOTOGRAPHY

CONTACT INFO



017-7583911



weijietan90@gmail.com



Gemas, Negeri Sembilan

TAN WEI JIE

Bachelor of Design with Honours

I am a fresh graduate gaming design student from UPSI. In these 4 years of studies, I have mastered Unity, Blender, AI, PS, PR and some other common design adobe software with certain knowledge.

WORK EXPERIENCE

UPSI

2019 - 2022

- Member of the Scene Design Team for Pesta Chun.
- Design Team Leader for The 4th National Chinese Language Literary Camp.
- Volunteering as a Photographer for the FYP Fashion Design Showcase.
- Design Team and Online Exhibition Leader for Chinese Traditional Culture event.
- Freelancer

2022

- I serve as the Design Team Leader for 30-Hour Frmine and I'm also responsible for editing the event video.
- Engaged by the Chinese Society UPSI to Design an Online 3D Exhibition.
- Engaged to create educational animation videos.

CreativeTank

Mar 2023 - Aug 2023

- I handled the position of a 2D game developer for 6 months during my industrial training.
- I used Unity, Photoshop, and Illustrator for various game-related tasks such as creating map icons, debugging, animating characters, and setting up in-game tasks.
- Voiceover for NPCs in the game 'Dapur Mili'.
- I used Blender to create a 3D logo for 'Dapur Mili' and worked on the LNG project, creating 3D assets for data analysis. Additionally, I fixed rigging issues for the LNG engineer character.
- At the Program Animasi Blender organized by MDEC for teachers across Malaysia, I served as the photographer for CreativeTank's project and also assisted instructors in teaching teachers the fundamentals of Blender.
- I create a simple Virtual Reality project using Unity for the company my colleague.
- Sin Chew Media **Corporation Berhad**
 - 2024-now
- Editor of the young people's publication "Xue Hai".
- Editor in charge of the first page of the youth newspaper every Friday.
- Head of student journalists in the kl area.

EDUCATION

Sekolah Menengah Kebangsaan Gemas

2012-2016

SPM

BM (C+), BI (D), P.Moral (B+), Sejarah (B), Maths (A), P.Seni (B+), AddMaths (C+), Physics (D), Chemistry (E), Biology (E), BC (A-)

Sekolah Menengah Kebangsaan Tuanku Abdul Rahman

STPM (CGPA 2.83)

2017-2018

Pengajian Am (A-), Geografi (B),

Ekonomi (C+), Pengajian Perniagaan (C+)

Universiti Pendidikan Sultan Idris (UPSI)

2019 - 2023

DEGREE (CGPA 3.74)

Bachelor of Design (Digital Games) with Honours (AC33)

SKILLS

Drawing

Game Development

Graphic Design **Painting**



Game Design



SOFTWARE







